Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Other labor organizations correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 4; 3 microfilm reels
  - National Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1941, 1948-1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 13)
  - National Farm Labor Union, 1946-1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 14)
  - National Women's Trade Union League of America, 1922 1941- 1950; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 15)
  - New York Teamster Organizations, 1921; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 16)
  - Office Employees International Union, 1941 1943, 1946 -1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 17)
  - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Finishers International Association, 1941 1947- 1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 18)
  - Pattern Makers League of North America, 1923- 1925; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 19)
  - Progressive Mine Workers of America, 1939 1943- 1945; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 20)
  - Retail Clerks International Protective Association, 1940- 1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 21)
  - Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 770, Oakland, California, 1949- 1950; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 22)
  - Seafarers International Union of North America, 1942, 1945,1948-1950,1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 23)
  - Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1942, 1949- 1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 24)
  - Stove Mounters International Union of North America, 1941, 1948- 1950; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 25)
  - Tobacco Workers International Union, 1923, 1949- 1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 26)
  - Trades and Labor Congress of Canada, 1941- 1942, 1948- 1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 27)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, 1942- 1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 28)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft, Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1941- 1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 29)
  - United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1946, 1948, 1950; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 30)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1907, 1941, 1944- -1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 31)
  - United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, 1941- 1942,1946,1949,1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 32)
  - United Garment Workers of America, 1941- 1943, undated; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 33)
  - United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 34)
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1921, 1942-1948; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 35)
  - United Teamsters of America, 1907-1908; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 36)
  - United Textile Workers of America, 1921-1922,1939,1949-1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 37)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1922, 1941-1943, 1947, 1949-1951; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 38)
  - Workers Defense League, 1941-1952; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 39)
  - Workers' Education Bureau of America, 1923-1925, 1941-1947; Series 4 (Reel 78, Segment 40)
- General correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 5; 8 microfilm reels
  The general correspondence documents the I.B.T.'s relationships with the general public and non-labor organizations. Again, the great majority of material dates in the 1940's. A large segment consists of exchanges with the United States government, mainly during World War II, and concerns both cooperative and regulative activities made necessary by the war. There are also files for several trucking and freight companies, employer associations, and many charitable organizations.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent, organization, or subject and chronological thereunder. Following the titles under each letter of the alphabet is a miscellaneous file for that letter containing exchanges that total only one or two items.
  - A & P Tea Company, 1942-1950; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 1)
  - Acme Fast Freight, Inc., 1942; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 2)
  - Akers Motor Lines, Inc., 1942, 1947, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 3)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1943-1944; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 4)
  - American Cancer Society, Inc., 1947-1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 5)
  - American Committee to Aid the University of Nymegen, 1948-1949; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 6)
  - American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1947-1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 7)
  - American Heart Association, Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 7)
    See: Heart Fund
  - American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1941, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 8)
  - American Railway Express Company, 1919-1922; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 9)
  - American Railway Express Company, 1923; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 10)
  - American Railway Express Company, 1924; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 11)
  - American Red Mogen David for Israel, Inc., 1949-1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 12)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 13)
  - American Trucking Association, 1937, 1942. -1951; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 14)
  - American Trucking Association - Local Cartage National Conference, 1943-1948, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 15)
  - Anderson, Victor E., 1944, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 16)
  - Anonymous, 1939, 1944- -1952, n.d.; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 17)
  - Associated General Contractors, 1938, 1940- -1946; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 18)
  - Associated General Contractors, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 19)
  - Associated General Contractors, 1948-1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 20)
  - Associated Pipe Line Contractors, 1948-1951; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 21)
  - Associated Transport, Inc., 1942-1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 22)
  - Auerbach Educational Productions, 1949-1950; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 23)
  - Aa - American A, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 24)
  - American - American M, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 25)
  - American N - Az, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 26)
  - Bechtel Corporation, 1947-1951; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 27)
  - Bernays, Edward L., 1943-1944; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 28)
  - Blaw Knox Construction Company, 1948, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 29)
  - Borden Company, 1944-1946; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 29)
  - Borden Company, 1944-1946; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 30)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1946, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 31)
  - Brake, E. E., 1949-1950; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 32)
  - (The) Bramwood Company, 1912-1913; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 33)
  - Brandeis Memorial Colony, 1942; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 34)
  - Braun (C. F.) and Company, 1949-1951; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 35)
  - Bookwalter-Ball-Greathouse Printing Company, 1940-1948; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 36)
  - Brown, Leo C., S. J., 1949; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 37)
  - Brown and Root Construction Company, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 38)
  - Ba - Bn, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 40)
  - Bo - Bz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 41)
  - Carolina Motor Express Company, 1949-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 1)
  - Catalytic Construction Company, 1947-1951; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1945-1946, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 3)
  - (The) Christian Science Monitor, 1949-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 3a)
  - Citizen Food Committee, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 4)
  - Committee of Catholics for Human Rights, 1944; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 5)
  - Commonwealth Club of California, 1947, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 6)
  - Community Chest Campaigns, 1947-1951; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 7)
  - (The) Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., 1941-1952; Series 5 (Reel 79, Segment 39)
  - Conventions, 1940-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 8)
  - Council for Democracy, 1942-1949; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 9)
  - Credit Union National Association, Inc., 1947-1950; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 10)
  - Cruice, Daniel L., 1907-1908; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 11)
  - Crusade for Freedom, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 12)
  - Ca - Cd, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 13)
  - Ce - Cn, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 14)
  - Coa - Con, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 15)
  - Coo - Cz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 16)
  - Daniels Motor Freight, Inc., 1949-1951; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 17)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1924, 1932, 1934, 1936, 1940-1943; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 18)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1944-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 19)
  - Dickens, Randolph, Jr. vs. I.B.T. and Tobin, 1947-1948; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 20)
  - Donnellan, George, 1941-1942; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 21)
  - Donnellan, Michael J., 1940-1941; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 22)
  - Douglas, Melvyn, 1941; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 23)
  - Dowell, A. Yates, 1940-1943; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 24)
  - Da - Dz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 25)
  - Ebasco Services, Inc., 1950-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 26)
  - Ecklund, Richard P., 1950; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 27)
  - Edwards, Frank, 1949-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 28)
  - European Recovery Program, 1947-1948; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 29)
  - Evans, N. W., 1908, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 30)
  - Ea - Ez, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 30a)
    The original finding aid has this title as part of folder 30. For digital object creation purposes the reel and segment must be unique numbers. Therefore, this segment has been designated 30a.
  - Farley, James A., 1941-1942; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 31)
  - Feinsinger, Nathan P., 1947; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 32)
  - Fight for Freedom, Inc., 1941-1944, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 33)
  - Ford, Sam C., 1942; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 34)
  - Fortune, 1941-1945, 1951-; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 35)
  - Fa - Fz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 35)
  - Gamble - Robinson Produce Company, 1946-1951; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 36)
  - Goldblatt Brothers, Inc., 1947-1948; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 37)
  - Gompers, Sam, 1944-1952; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 38)
  - Gramling, John C., 1942, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 39)
  - Ga - Go, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 40)
  - Gp - Gz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 80, Segment 41)
  - Harvard University, 1942, 1947, 1951-1952; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 1)
  - Hayes Freight Lines, 1941-1950; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 2)
  - Hearst Newspapers, 1941-1942, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 3)
  - Heart Fund, 1950-1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 4)
  - Hennis Trucking Company, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 5)
  - Hobbs Bill, 1946; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 6)
  - Hotels, 1921-1922, 1938-1952; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 7)
  - Ha - Hn, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 8)
  - Ho - Hz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 9)
  - Indiana (State of), 1941-1950; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 10)
  - Indiana Democratic State Central Committee, 1941-1945; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 11)
  - Indiana Farm Bureau Cooperative Association, Inc., 1942-1944; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 12)
  - Indiana Motor Truck Association, Inc., 1942, 1949- -1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 13)
  - Indiana National Bank, 1941-1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 14)
  - Indianapolis Newspapers, 1941-1949; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 15)
  - Infantile Paralysis, 1942-1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 15)
  - International Labor Office, 1941-1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 16)
  - International Labor Press of America, 1922-1924, 1941- 1951; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 17)
  - International Teamster - Comments on New Format, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 18)
  - International Teamster - Miscellaneous, 1908, 1942- -1950; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 19)
  - Interstate Motor Freight System, 1940-1942, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 20)
  - la - Iz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 21)
  - Ja - Jz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 22)
  - Keefer, E. D., 1942-1943; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 23)
  - Keenan, Joseph B., 1942; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 24)
  - Keeshin, J. L., 1941-1945; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 25)
  - Kraft Foods Company, 1942-1943, 1947, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 26)
  - Kroger Company, 1945-1952; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 27)
  - Ka - Kz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 28)
  - La Follette, Robert M., 1941, 1946; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 29)
  - Leventhal, Louis, 1938-1942, 1945- 1947; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 30)
  - Lord, James R., 1940-1941, 1947, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 31)
  - La - Le, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 81, Segment 32)
  - Lf - Lz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 1)
  - M and M Transportation Company, 1943; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 2)
  - McLean Trucking Company, 1049-1950; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 3)
  - Malarney, Robert D., 1946-1949; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 4)
  - Matheson, Dixon and Brady, 1941-1942, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 5)
  - Miami Property, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 5)
    See: Keefer, E. D.
  - Michigan (State of), 1946, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 6)
  - Midwest Operators Association, 1947, 1950- •1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 7)
  - Midwest Transfer Company, 1949-1950; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 8)
  - Moffet Studio, Chicago, 111., 1940-1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 9)
  - Morrison - Knudsen Company, Inc., 1948-1949, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 10)
  - Motor Carriers Association of St, Louis, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 11)
  - Ma, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 12)
  - Mb - Mn, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 12)
  - Mo - Mz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 13)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1943, 1945, 1949. -1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 14)
  - National Biscuit Company, 1942-1944, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 15)
  - (The) National Civic Federation, 1942-1945; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 16)
  - (skipped), Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 17)
  - National Committee for Traffic Safety, 1946-1948, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 18)
  - National Committee to Abolish the Poll Tax, 1941-1943; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 19)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc., 1943-1946; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 20)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties, 1942-1945; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 21)
  - (The) National Grange, 1940, 1944; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 22)
  - National Joint Automobile Transporters Committee, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 23)
  - National Rubber Committee, 1943; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 24)
  - National Urban League, 1943, 1946 -1947,, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 25)
  - Nationally Organized Railway Labor. Organizations Qualified to Participate in the Formation of the National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1942-1944, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 26)
  - New York World, 1921-1925; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 27)
  - Naa - National D, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 28)
  - National E - Nd, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 29)
  - Ne - Nz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 30)
  - O'Connell, John, 1948, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 31)
  - O'Dwyer, William, 1946; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 32)
  - Omar, Incorporated, 1945-1948; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 33)
  - Owner-Operator Trucks, 1941, 1949- -1950; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 34)
  - Oa - Oz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 35)
  - Pegler, Westbrook, 1941-1942, 1946, 1948,1952; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 36)
  - Pilot Freight Carriers, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 37)
  - Port of New York Authority, 1949, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 38)
  - Pa - Pz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 82, Segment 39)
  - Quayle, Oliver A., Jr., 1939-1942; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 1)
  - Qua - Quz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 2)
  - Ransdell, Incorporated, 1946-1948; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 3)
  - Ransdell, Incorporated, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 4)
  - Ransdell, Incorporated, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 5)
  - Ransdell, Incorporated, 1951; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 6)
  - Ransdell, Incorporated, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 7)
  - Reilly Tar and Chemical Corporation, 1940-1941; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 8)
  - Resolutions, 1940, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 9)
  - Rickenbacker, E. V., 1944, 1946; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 10)
  - Riesel, Victor, 1950-1952; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1940-1942, 1948- 1952; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 12)
  - Ra - Ri, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 13)
  - Rk - Rz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 14)
  - Sabath, A. J., 1943, 1945- 1946; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 15)
  - Safeway Stores, Inc., 1943, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 16)
  - San Jacinto Ordnance Depot, 1941-1942; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 17)
  - Seventh-day Adventist Council on Industrial Relations, 1946-1948, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 18)
  - Shell Oil Company, 1944-1952; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 19)
  - Shelley, John F., 1940, 1944- • 1946; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 20)
  - Southeastern Motor Truck Lines, 1942, 1945, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 21)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare, 1945-1947; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 22)
  - Southwestern Transportation Company, 1942-1943, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 23)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1941, 1943; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 24)
  - Stelzle, Charles, 1940-1941, 1943, 1946-1947; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 25)
  - Sa - SI, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 26)
  - Sm - Sz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 27)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1948; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 28)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1945-1952; Series 5 (Reel 83, Folder 29)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1945-1952; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 30)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1943, 1945, 1949- -1950; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 31)
  - Tobin, Maurice J., 1940-1944; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 32)
  - Tobriner, Matthew O., 1940, 1942- 1943, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 33)
  - Toner, Jerome L., 1941-1942, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 34)
  - Tournamixer, 1948-1949; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 35)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1941-1946, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 36)
  - Ta - Th, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 83, Segment 37)
  - Ti - Tz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 1)
  - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1942, 1946-1947; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 2)
  - Union Trust Company, 1923, 1941-1950; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 3)
  - U.S. - Agriculture, Department of, 1940-1943, 1947; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 4)
  - U.S. - Air Force, Department of the, 1948; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 5)
  - U.S. - Army - Military Government, Office of, 1947, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 6)
  - U.S. - Atomic Energy Commission, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 7)
  - U.S. - Censorship, Office of, 1944; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 8)
  - U.S. - Commerce, Department of, 1946-1951; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 9)
  - U.S. - Congress, Members of, 1937, 1940-1944; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 10)
  - U.S. - Congress, Members of, 1945-1948; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 11)
  - U.S. - Congress, Members of, 1949-1952, n.d.; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 12)
  - U.S. - Defense, Department of, 1949-1952; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 13)
  - U.S. - Defense Production Administration, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 14)
  - U.S. - Economic Cooperation Administration, 1949-1951, undated; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 15)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency, 1951-1952; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 16)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board, 1946-1952; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 17)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board and Conferences and Miscellaneous Area Groups, 1951-1952 (organized alphabetically by state concerned); Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 18)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board and Joint Councils, 1951-1952 (organized by joint council number); Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 19)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board and Locals 1-199, 1951-1952; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 20)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board and Locals 200-399, by local number); Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 21)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board and Locals 400-599, Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 22)
  - U.S. - Economic Stabilization Agency - Wage Stabilization Board and Locals 600-899, Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 23)
  - U.S. - Economic Warfare, Board of, 1942; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 24)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for, 1942-1943; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 25)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - Defense Transportation, Office of, 1942-1945; Series 5 (Othertype 84, Folder 26)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - Defense Transportation, Office of - Notices and Orders of Terminations, 1945, A-Z; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 27)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - National War Labor Board, 1942-1943; Series 5 (Reel 84, Segment 28)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - National War Labor Board, 1944-1945; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 1)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - National War Labor Board - Trucking Commission, 1943-1945; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 2)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - Production Management, Office of, 1941-1942; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 3)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - War Manpower Commission, 1942-1944; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 4)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - War Production Board, 1942-1945; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 5)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - War Production Board - Shipbuilding Stabilization Committee, 1942-1943; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 6)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - War Production Board - Shipbuilding Stabilization Committee, 1944; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 7)
  - U.S. - Emergency Management, Office for - War Production Board - Shipbuilding Stabilization Committee, 1945-1946; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 8)
  - U.S. - Employees' Compensation Commission, 1941; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 9)
  - U.S. - Federal Civil Defense Administration 1952, Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 10)
  - U.S. - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 1947-1951; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 11)
  - U.S. - Federal Security Agency, 1941, 1950 i; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 12)
  - U.S. - Federal Works Agency, 1941, 1945- -1950; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 13)
  - U.S. - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 14)
  - U.S. - Interior, Department of the, 1941, 1948, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 15)
  - U.S. - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1941-1948; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 16)
  - U.S. - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 17)
  - U.S. - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1950-1952; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 18)
  - U.S. - Justice, Department of, 1940-1947, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 18)
  - U.S. - Labor, Department of, 1935-1937, 1940-1946; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 19)
  - U.S. - Labor, Department of, 1947-1952; Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 20)
  - U.S. - Labor, Department of - Ship-building Stabilization Committee, Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 21)
    See: U. S. - Emergency Management, Office for - War Production Board
  - U.S. - Labor, Department of - Wage, Series 5 (Reel 85, Segment 21)
  - U.S. - Labor, Department of - Wage, 1944-1946; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 1)
  - U.S. - Mutual Security Agency, 1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 2)
  - U.S. - National Labor Relations Board, 1938-1944; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 3)
  - U.S. - National Labor Relations Board, 1945-1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 4)